<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Basics on Cap'n Hugo Relearrrn Theme</title><link>https://adpit.github.io/arie_digital/pir/basics.html</link><description>Recent content in Basics on Cap'n Hugo Relearrrn Theme</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>pir</language><atom:link href="https://adpit.github.io/arie_digital/pir/basics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What's New</title><link>https://adpit.github.io/arie_digital/pir/basics/migration.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://adpit.github.io/arie_digital/pir/basics/migration.html</guid><description>Arrr! Pirrrates Fello' pirrrates, grog made us dizzy! Be awarrre some stuff may look weird in this trrranslat'n. Like Merrrmaids, do'n math or chemistrrry and stuff.
This document shows ye what&amp;rsquo;s new 'n th' latest release. For a detailed list o' changes, see th' history plank.
0.95.0 Th' minimum required Cap'n Hugo version.
Break'n A change that requires act'n by ye after upgrad'n t' assure th' ship be still functional.</description></item><item><title>Requirrrements</title><link>https://adpit.github.io/arie_digital/pir/basics/requirements.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://adpit.github.io/arie_digital/pir/basics/requirements.html</guid><description>Thanks t' th' simplicity o' Cap'n Hugo, this plank be as empty as this theme needs requirements.
Just download at least version 0.95.0 o' th' Cap'n Hugo binary fer yer OS (Windows, Linux, Mac).</description></item><item><title>Installat'n</title><link>https://adpit.github.io/arie_digital/pir/basics/installation.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://adpit.github.io/arie_digital/pir/basics/installation.html</guid><description>Th' follow'n steps be here t' help ye initialize yer new website. If ye don&amp;rsquo;t know Cap'n Hugo at all, we strongly suggest ye learn more about it by follow'n this great documentat'n fer beginners.
Create yer project Cap'n Hugo provides a new command t' create a new website.
hugo new ship &amp;lt;new_project&amp;gt;Install th' theme Install th' Relearrrn theme by follow'n this documentat'n us'n Hugo&amp;rsquo;s module system.
This theme&amp;rsquo;s repository be: https://github.</description></item><item><title>Configurrrat'n</title><link>https://adpit.github.io/arie_digital/pir/basics/configuration.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://adpit.github.io/arie_digital/pir/basics/configuration.html</guid><description>Global ship parameters On top o' Cap'n Hugo global configurat'n, th' Relearrrn theme lets ye define th' follow'n parameters 'n yer config.toml (here, values be default).
Avast that some o' these parameters be explained 'n details 'n other sections o' this documentat'n.
[params] # This controls whether submenus will be expanded (true), or collapsed (false) 'n th' # menu; if no sett'n be given, th' first menu level be set t' false, all others t' true; # this can be overridden 'n th' planks frontmatter alwaysopen = true # Prefix URL t' edit current plank.</description></item><item><title>Customizat'n</title><link>https://adpit.github.io/arie_digital/pir/basics/customization.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://adpit.github.io/arie_digital/pir/basics/customization.html</guid><description>Th' Relearrrn theme has been built t' be as configur'ble as poss'ble by defin'n multiple partials
In themes/hugo-theme-relearn/layouts/partials/, ye will find all th' partials defined fer this theme. If ye need t' overwrite someth'n, don&amp;rsquo;t change th' code directly. Instead follow this plank. You&amp;rsquo;d create a new partial 'n th' layouts/partials folder o' yer local project. This partial will have th' priority.
This theme defines th' follow'n partials :</description></item><item><title>Stylesheet generrrat'r</title><link>https://adpit.github.io/arie_digital/pir/basics/generator.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://adpit.github.io/arie_digital/pir/basics/generator.html</guid><description>This interactive tool may help ye t' generate yer own color variant stylesheet.
Show usage instruct'ns T' get started, first select a color variant from th' variant switch 'n th' lower left sidebar that fits ye best as a start'n point.
Th' graph be interactive an' reflect th' current colors. Ye can click on any o' th' colored boxes t' adjust th' respective color. Th' graph an' th' plank will update accordingly.</description></item><item><title>Topbarrr Modificat'n</title><link>https://adpit.github.io/arie_digital/pir/basics/topbar.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://adpit.github.io/arie_digital/pir/basics/topbar.html</guid><description>Th' theme comes wit' a reasonably configured topbar.
Nevertheless, yer requirements may differ from this configurat'n. Luckily th' theme got ye covered as th' themebar, its buttons an' th' functionality behind these buttons be fully configur'ble by ye.
Smarrrt Arrrse All mentioned file names below can be clicked an' show ye th' implementat'n fer a better understand'n.
Areas Th' default configurat'n comes wit' three predefined areas that may contain an arbitrary set o' buttons.</description></item><item><title>Historrry</title><link>https://adpit.github.io/arie_digital/pir/basics/history.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://adpit.github.io/arie_digital/pir/basics/history.html</guid><description>Changelog 5.22.1 (2023-10-02) Enhancements [feature] i18n: add Swahili translat'n #666 [feature] math: hide unrendered math #663 [feature] tabs: improve a11y by remov'n duplicate hidden title #662 [feature] mermaid: improve zoom UX #659 Fixes [bug] variant: fix sidebar-flyout borders color fer zen #667 [bug] clipboard: fix RTL locat'n o' tooltip #661 [bug] clipboard: ignore RTL fer code #660 [bug] expand: fix aria-controls #658 [bug] theme: fix id generat'n fer markdownified titles #657 [bug] mermaid: avoid graph bomb'n on hugo &amp;ndash;minify #656 [bug] mermaid: fix width fer some graphs #655 5.</description></item></channel></rss>